A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18 FA290
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1979-2003 1987-2003; 4; 53.15 Cubic Feet microfilm reels representing 205 cubic feet of paper records.
  - University of Wisconsin - #20010118, Tabs 1-3, 1996 (Reel 505, Frame 613)
  - University of Washington - #20000325, 1990 (Reel 505, Frame 974)
    Carolyn Madden
  - University of Wisconsin - #20010118, Tabs 3 (continued)-10, 1996 (Reel 506, Frame 1)
  - University of Wisconsin - #980327, 1996 (Reel 506, Frame 334)
    Roger Williams
  - Urban Institute - #20000191, 1989 (Reel 506, Frame 483)
    Marilyn Moon
  - Urban Institute - #200010113, 1989 (Reel 506, Frame 672)
  - Urban Institute - #200010136, 1990 (Reel 507, Frame 1)
  - Urban Institute - #9101, 1998 (Reel 507, Frame 670)
    Richard Michel
  - Urban Institute - #94-119, 2000 (Reel 508, Frame 1)
  - Urban Institute - #95-46, 1994 (Reel 508, Frame 575)
  - Urban Institute - #96178, Tabs 1-2, 1995 (Reel 508, Frame 883)
  - Urban Institute - #96178, Tabs 3-10, 1995 (Reel 509, Frame 1)
  - Urban Institute - #96951, 1999 (Reel 509, Frame 516)
    Joshua Wiener
  - Urban Institute - #970267, 2000 (Reel 510, Frame 1)
    Corbin Liu
  - Urban Institute - #970272, 1998 (Reel 511, Frame 1)
  - Urban Institute - #970950, 2000 (Reel 512, Frame 1)
  - Urban Institute - #980180, 2000 (Reel 513, Frame 1)
  - Urban Institute - #980779, Tabs 1-3, 2000 (Reel 513, Frame 689)
  - Urban Institute - #980779, Tabs 4-10, 2000 (Reel 514, Frame 1)
  - Urban Institute - #990224, 1990 (Reel 514, Frame 185)
    Barbara Gage
  - Urban Institute - #990776, 1994 (Reel 514, Frame 336)
  - Urban Institute - #990806, 1994 (Reel 514, Frame 463)
    Gregory Acs
  - Vanderbilt University - #11192, 1995 (Reel 514, Frame 587)
    Colleen Conway-Welch
  - Vanderbilt University - #6838, 1996 (Reel 514, Frame 883)
    Richard Couto
  - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - #94-43, 1996 (Reel 514, Frame 887)
    William Rochford
  - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - #96039, 1996 (Reel 514, Frame 1064)
  - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - #96998, 1997 (Reel 514, Frame 1118)
  - Vanderbilt University School of Nursing - #94-21, 1997 (Reel 515, Frame 1)
  - Varicella Zoster Research Foundation, Inc. - #94-121, 1998 (Reel 515, Frame 165)
    Richard Perkin
  - Vera Institute of Justice, Inc. - #20010275, 1998 (Reel 515, Frame 419)
    Julia Vitullo-Martion
  - Vera Institute of Justice, Inc. - #95-51, 1999 (Reel 515, Frame 515)
    Christopher Stone and Julia Vitullo-Martion
  - Vera Institute of Justice, Inc. - #95-56, 1999 (Reel 515, Frame 628)
    Meryl Schwartz
  - Vera Institute of Justice, Inc. - #96638, 1989 (Reel 515, Frame 717)
  - Victim Services Agency - #92-54, 1991 (Reel 515, Frame 800)
    Frances Tyler
  - Victim Services, Inc. - #96527, 1993 (Reel 516, Frame 1)
  - Visiting Nurse Service - #980555, Tabs 1-3, 1998 (Reel 516, Frame 697)
    Christopher Murtaugh
  - Visiting Nurse Service - #980555, Tabs 4-10, 1998 (Reel 517, Frame 1)
  - Volunteer Trustees Foundation of Not-for-Profit Hospitals - #10012, 1996 (Reel 517, Frame 205)
    Linda Miller
  - Volunteer Trustees Foundation for Research and Education - #96208, 1993 (Reel 517, Frame 509)
  - Volunteer Trustees Foundation for Research and Education - #96620, Tabs 1-2, 1994 (Reel 517, Frame 668)
  - Volunteer Trustees Foundation for Research and Education - #96620, Tabs 3-10, 1994 (Reel 518, Frame 1)
  - Volunteer Trustees Foundation for Research and Education - #970595, 2001 (Reel 519, Frame 1)
  - Volunteer Trustees Foundation for Research and Education - #980443, Tabs 1-4, 1994 (Reel 519, Frame 634)
  - Volunteer Trustees Foundation for Research and Education - #980443, Tabs 4 (continued)-10, 1994 (Reel 520, Frame 1)
  - Volunteers of Legal Services - #9398, 1994 (Reel 520, Frame 258)
    Margaret Flint
  - Washington Hospital Center - #94-44, 1995 (Reel 520, Frame 386)
    Artencia Hawkins-Bell
  - Washington Hospital Center - #96040, 1991 (Reel 520, Frame 625)
    Carolyn Monford
  - Washington Hospital Center - #96999, 1996 (Reel 520, Frame 683)
  - Washington Tennis Foundation - #980802, 1998 (Reel 520, Frame 730)
    Kpakpundu Ezeze
  - Washington University - #93-93, 1987 (Reel 521, Frame 1)
    Robert Nease
  - We Care About New York - #10381, 1996 (Reel 521, Frame 431)
    Emory Jackson
  - We Care About New York - #91-15, 1996 (Reel 521, Frame 558)
  - Well Spouse Foundation - #91-67, 1997 (Reel 521, Frame 665)
    Peggy Meisel
  - Well Spouse Foundation - #94-134, 1998 (Reel 521, Frame 856)
    Patricia Still
  - Westat, Inc. - #10689, 1993 (Reel 522, Frame 1)
    Pat Skinner
  - William Carey College - #9251, 1993 (Reel 522, Frame 642)
    William Payne and Jim Edwards
  - WNYC Foundation - #93-81, 1995 (Reel 522, Frame 1022)
    Thomas Morgan
  - Women and Foundations - #10449, 1996 (Reel 523, Frame 1)
    Joanne Hayes
  - Women and Foundations - #11169, 1998 (Reel 523, Frame 97)
  - Women and Foundations - #8750, 1992 (Reel 523, Frame 156)
  - Women and Foundations - #90-54, 1986 (Reel 523, Frame 216)
    Jane Ransom
  - Women and Foundations - #91-77, 1990 (Reel 523, Frame 336)
  - Women and Foundations - #92-60, 1990 (Reel 523, Frame 460)
  - Women and Foundations - #92-70, 1994 (Reel 523, Frame 527)
  - Women and Foundations - #93-66, 1988 (Reel 523, Frame 593)
  - Women and Foundations - #94-102, 1991 (Reel 523, Frame 687)
    Walteen Grady Truly
  - Women and Foundations - #9882, 1993 (Reel 523, Frame 746)
  - Women and Philanthropy, Inc. - #95-90, 1988 (Reel 523, Frame 875)
  - Women's Prison Association and Home, Inc. - #92-27, 1989 (Reel 524, Frame 1)
    Ann Jacobs
  - Women's Prison Association and Home, Inc. - #95824, 1986 (Reel 524, Frame 95)
  - Women's Research and Education Institute - #94-120, 1990 (Reel 524, Frame 206)
    Cynthia Costello
  - Women's Research and Education Institute - #95-40, Tabs 1-3, 1991 (Reel 524, Frame 306)
    Barbara Krimgold
  - Women's Research and Education Institute - #95-40, Tabs 4-10, 1991 (Reel 525, Frame 1)
  - Women's Research and Education Institute - #970420, 1992 (Reel 525, Frame 283)
    Betty Parsons Dooley
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - #95-71, 1992 (Reel 525, Frame 341)
    Walter Reich
  - World Bank - #970423, 1993 (Reel 525, Frame 448)
    George Schieber
  - Wright State University - #11177, 1994 (Reel 525, Frame 512)
    Marshall Kapp
  - Wright State University - #90-76, 1987 (Reel 526, Frame 1)
  - Xavier University of Louisiana - #91-91, 1995 (Reel 526, Frame 422)
    J. W. Carmichael
  - Yale University - #11186, 1991 (Reel 526, Frame 530)
    Lisa Berkman
  - Yale University - #20020119, 1995 (Reel 526, Frame 873)
    Sharon Inouye
  - Yale University - #6073, 1994 (Reel 527, Frame 1)
    Elisa Manuelidis
  - Yale University - #94-90, 1994 (Reel 527, Frame 371)
  - Yale University - #95-47, 1997 (Reel 528, Frame 1)
    Charles Torre
  - Yale University - #970487, 1995 (Reel 528, Frame 640)
    Julie Lee
  - Yale University - #97063, 1997 (Reel 528, Frame 712)
    Terry Fried
  - Yale University - #980883, 1989 (Reel 528, Frame 919)
    Theodore Marmor
  - Youthbuild U.S.A. - #95-22, 1990 (Reel 529, Frame 1)
    Dorothy Stoneman
  - YWCA - #92-50, 1991 (Reel 529, Frame 526)
    Alpha Alexander
  - Zero to Three: National Center for Infants Toddlers and Families - #20000104, 1989 (Reel 529, Frame 602)
    Emily Fenichel